https://www.mediafast.com/privacy-policy/

1-888-756-8890
sales@mediafast.com
Privacy Policy
MediaFast considers protecting your online privacy a serious matter. This Privacy Statement explains our views and practices concerning privacy and how they may pertain to you as a user of our website.
Throughout this policy, “you” or “your” means you as a participant or user of the mediafast.com website. Also, “we” or “our” or “our site” means us or mediafast.com.
Section 1 – What we do with your information
When you browse our site, we automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. It also helps us improve the user experience for other users.
Additionally, we sometimes do email marketing and retargeting. With your permission, we may send you information about products, free content, premium content and special events.
Section 2 – Consent
Whenever you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, place an order, verify a credit card, arrange for a delivery, or return a purchase, we assume you consent to our collecting and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a different reason, like for a newsletter subscription or marketing messages, we will ask you directly for your expressed consent and provide you with an opportunity to withdraw your consent.
You can withdraw your consent at any time by clicking an “unsubscribe” link in a message we sent you or by contacting ahafen@mymediafast.com via email. Also, you can contact us by mail at 767 S. Auto Mall Dr. Warehouse #8, American Fork, UT 84003.
Section 3 – Disclosure
We may disclose your personal information if we are required to do so by law or if you violate our Terms of Service. Also, if our site is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so they may continue to sell and support our products and services.
IMPORTANT: We do not sell, rent or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties, including but not limited to advertisers, strategic partners or vendors.
Again, we consider protecting your online privacy a serious matter.
Section 4 – Third Party Services
In general, the third party providers used by us will only collect, use, and disclose your information to the extent necessary so they can perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, like payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by them.
In particular, certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in different jurisdictions than either you or us. So, if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway in the United States, your personal information used in completing the transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our company’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Section 5 – Links
Be aware that when you click on links on our site, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites and encourage you to read their Privacy Policies and Terms of Service.
Section 6 – Security
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow best practices in the industry to ensure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
Section 7 – Cookies
Digital Marketer utilizes cookies to create a more customized experience for our users and customers. We also use tracking pixels, like Google Analytics, to help in measuring and tracking where our website traffic is coming from and to analyze the performance of our site.
Also, we use remarking pixels from Facebook and Google to help in customized, targeted follow up advertising.
Section 8 – Age of consent
By using this site, you represent you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence and have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
Section 9 – Changes to this privacy policy
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time and we ask that you review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on our site. If we make material changes to this policy, the notifications will be posted here to make you aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
Section 10 – Questions and contact information
If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, or if you would like to register a complaint, or if you simply want more information, please contact our Privacy Compliance Officer.
She can be reached at ahafen@mymediafast.com or by mail sent to 767 S. Auto Mall Drive Warehouse #8, American Fork, UT 84003
Search for:
Free Video Brochure Sample
Recent Posts
Follow-Up After Distributing A Video Brochure Will Skyrocket Profits
Videos Have Drastically Improved Point Of Purchase Displays
Video Mailers Get Your Target Audience To Call You Back
Make More Sales With A Video Gift or Sample Box
Video Brochures Turn Potential Customers Into Paying Customers
Recent Commentsfilm on How Video Boxes Turn Samples Into Huge Profit-Makersfilm on How Video Boxes Turn Samples Into Huge Profit-Makersfilm on How Video Boxes Turn Samples Into Huge Profit-Makerserotik izle on How Video Boxes Turn Samples Into Huge Profit-Makerserotik on How Video Boxes Turn Samples Into Huge Profit-Makers Archives
December 2020
November 2020
October 2020
September 2020
August 2020
July 2020
June 2020
May 2020
